

# **Chia Hamid Ahmed**

Curriculum Vitae

**Phone** 

07705462272

Email

chiadawdi94@gmail.com

Address

Sulaymaniyah , Kani ba

## **Profile Info**

Date Of Birth: 3/12/1994

Nationality: Kurdish Marital Status: Single

Gender: Male

LinkedIn: chia hamid

### **General Skills**

Organization

Analysis

Information Technology

Social Level

# **Summary**

I am Chia Hamid, born in 1994. I graduated from the Department of Computer Science at Sulaimani University in 2016 to 2017. I have more than 5 years of experience in the field of accounting . I have a great desire to learn in all fields and can work under pressure. I have very good technology skills and have worked in several fields of technology and programming as a website designer .And I am always looking to learn new things and I have a great desire to learn.

#### **Educations**

University: Sulaimanyah University

Collage: Basic Education

Department : Computer Science Degree : Bachelor - Graduated Year of graduate : 2016 - 2017

# **Computer Skills**

MS Office

Web Development

Programming

Mobile Application

Outlook

Hardware

Software

UI/UX Design

# **Training and Certificate**

- 1. Google CompTIA A+ exam practice Certificate By (Coursera).
- 2.Technical Support Fundamentals (Google IT Support Professional Certificate).
- 3. Two certificates by Re:coded about (Front-end development) and (Introduction to data).
- 4. Having Five Certificates as a Web Developer in Two Stage.
- 5. Customer Service Skills That Are Crucial For Positive Experience(April 2018).
- 6. Critical Elements of Customer Service(Online Cores 2019).
- 7. Hidden Secrets of Selling Tips & Techniques in Alison (Online cores 2019)

## Language

Kurdish  $\star \star \star \star \star$ English  $\star \star \star \star \star$ Arabic  $\star \star \star \star \star$ 

## **Experience**

#### Pc Net Company

Aug 2017 - Aug2018

Customer sales and Accouter

Pc Net Company Sales and Accounts Management, Share the offers and solutions with Clients and follow up with them. Find & deal with customers and contract with them and full service (pre sales & after sales) for the clients and share monthly Bills with customers with follow up them for pay their bills monthly.

- ? Salesdeveloping and marketing.
- 2 Daily following up the situation of the market to know the situation of thecompetitors.
- Preparing daily reports of sales and send them to the upper manager.
- 2 Merchandising sales by using negotiation skills.

#### Haloy Slimani Company

Aug 2018 - Nov2019

Accoutant and Customer service

Accountant and Customer service for exchanging money and Remittances inside Iraq .and exchange between currency.

- Accountant Company.
- Sending and receiving Money.
- Customer Sales

#### Shabaka Al nakdia Company

Dec 2019 - Jan2021

Accoutant and Customer service

Accountant and Customer service for exchanging money and Remittances inside Iraq .and exchange between currency.

- Accountant Company.
- Sending and receiving Money.
- Customer Sales

### Tazhan Company

Feb 2021 - present

Accounting Manager and Office Manager

Accounting Manager and office Manager in Tazhan company for General contracting.

- accounting Manager.
- office Manager.
- Customer Sales .